what's up guys welcome back to another
set and forget pod so I mean this is a
very well overdue pod you know everybody
Do's Community it's time the time is
here we finally are doing the center
forer pod with do I've been uh we've
been meaning to do this for like two
three months already bro so like yeah
bro so so talk to me bro like what's up
you're on you're on here what's up I
know man it's been a minute man I
appreciate you having me on here man for
real so I mean you just came back from
Detroit right now you were over at your
hometown right yeah I just came back so
how was like how does it feel cuz like
for me personally like whenever cuz I I
I used to live in like a certain part of
Miami and then I mov now to a different
part of Miami not far probably like 20
30 minutes and whenever I go back to
like my old part where like I used to
live I don't want to say like I get like
anxiety but like I want to leave that
area like as soon as possible like as
soon as I want cuz it gives me like I
don't say like withdrawals but I don't
know like I just don't feel good cuz
like I worked so hard to get out of
there like I wasn't in the hood or
nothing but like just that area reminds
me of like a bunch of like negative
stuff like a bunch of like bad stuff
that happen now this is like a new
chapter in my life so I tried to like
avoid that right even when I have to go
see my parents I'm like yo just like
pull it to my crib you know like I'm not
trying to go over there so how was it
for you when you go back home now um
when I went back home it was really a
humbling experience for me like just
seeing like the stuff that I worked so
hard to get away from when I came back
it was just like okay you came a long
way like I it really made me appreciate
how far I've came when I came back back
home but it was good to see my family
but it just really made me want to go
harder when I came back for sure you
have any siblings or is just you yeah I
got one sister and one brother yeah
you're the youngest or sir you're the
youngest I'm the youngest how like like
what like what are they up to um my
sister she is into like Amazon so she's
like selling stuff on Amazon and she
still Trac um my brother he's like a
coach so he just do like football just
coaching and they're still in your
hometown like in Detroit yes yes so then
how do they feel like that you came out
over here like they see you like like
what the [__] you doing
like I mean they just you know they
happy for me like they just happy for me
um they still kind of like mind blown of
like the the transformation over the
years cuz like I still was like a reg
like they don't view me as like some
sort of celebrity or or um somebody
that's just not the same person I'm
still the same but it just like they
they will really listen to what I have
to say now you know so you didn't leave
like your hometown I don't want to say
they didn't like really believe in you
but they didn't think it was possible
like you were going to do that um I
really don't know I was really to myself
during my journey like I really wasn't
like oh family see look at this look at
what I'm doing like it wasn't like that
it was just me just grinding trying to
get out of my job to take it to the next
level so I wasn't really broadcasting to
my family like that they have to watch
my YouTube channel and I don't even know
if they was watching my YouTube channel
so I don't I don't really know so then
how how was like your journey because we
have very similar Journeys when it comes
to like not coming from much you get me
like we had to like literally get like
what we wanted we had to grind for it
right how was how was your journey I
know you did a whole video on it which I
looked at all the videos and I'm just
like holy [__] this guy's just like me
you just actually journeyed it I didn't
Journey it which like looking back at it
now and kind of like what I tell
everybody now like bro Journey your [__]
man you got to document it you document
it you look back week after week month
after month you're like damn last week I
was here now I'm here I'm actually doing
better right like why why did you
Journey like why did you put it on
YouTube like what was the purpose behind
that um I just wanted to show people
that it was possible to take trading to
the next level and be able to quit your
job um I think that's like all the
Traders goals is to get out of their job
and just trade fulltime but um you want
me to talk about like the the whole man
okay so I went to Western Michigan
University I was uh I was a graphic
design major and I just learned quickly
like this is not what I want to do this
is not this is not going to get me to
the point where I want to be at
financially so um I dropped out on my
senior year of college and um I started
I made a YouTube channel I had a YouTube
channel before I even had the Channel
that I have today and um I was just
doing like reaction videos like I just
had a passion for like recording like I
always like making YouTube videos so um
I stopped doing that I don't know why um
I just wasn't really super passionate
about it I just like making YouTube
videos then I got into Drop Shipping um
I was doing a couple sales but I wasn't
motivated I don't really know why I just
kept quitting but it I just know that
really wasn't for me so um I stopped the
Drop Shipping and then um I found Forex
and I ran into IML so nice IML shout out
to IML um in a way in a way shout out to
them yeah shout out to if I would not
gotten recruited I wouldn't be here
either so 100% yeah 100% um so yeah I
got an IML I was there for like four to
five months um learn the basics like a
little bit of Market structure like just
basic stuff and then I got out I just
quit because I just knew that that they
really didn't want you to be
independently trading so they wanted me
to rely on them I'm like I'm good so I
left um I end up buying fibs online
course I don't know if you know who I
know exactly okay I bought his course
and I was doing fibs a little bit I had
to tweak tweak his strategy a little bit
um so it can be better for me um I was
making some money from it but at that
time I still wanted to be versatile in
the market I didn't want to just see the
see my like the market in one way so I
kind of like gravitated away from
Fibonacci and I really implemented
Supply demand into my um my strategy and
um yeah I kind of just took it to the
next level after that I'm not going to
lie so then like at what point like
because obviously like for me like what
it took me to buy the first car get my
own crib like do all these moves like I
had like a certain goal in mind it's
like a certain dollar amount right like
I wanted to have this x amount in my
account in order for me to make this
move so I have like that room to like
move around like when did you make or
when did you know to make that move was
it like a certain dollar amount was it
like yo like I just know what's going to
happen in the future future you just
took the leap like how do you know to
take that next step or how did you take
the next step so you are you asking me
the amount that I was comfortable with
no like like what like what did you have
to like do in order to take that step to
leave and come to Miami like what did
you need like did you need a certain
amount you don't have to say the amount
just like is was it money was it the
skill set was it like the strategy that
it finally clicked like what made you
make that move um it was it was a little
bit of everything honestly like it was I
needed a large account that was number
one I needed to have a large trading
account so I can be able to actually
afford to be here cuz it cost a lot to
even live here so um the strategy wise I
already was kind of like confident with
the strategy I was using so I was
already like consistently profitable
before I quit my job and before I moved
out here so it was just me having large
sums of money in my trading account like
I needed to have a large account I
couldn't make 500 700 in a day and be
able to live here like I just couldn't
do it so I needed large sum of money for
sure okay so it was like a little BX
like a mix of everything right I feel
like for me like like you for sure did
it like a little bit more aggressive I
was like more conservative I'm like yo
like until I know I can't live a full
year without like the money that I have
saved which at the time my expenses are
probably like anywhere from like 2 to 3K
like if I don't have like 15 to 20K
saved up like I can't make this move
because I'll literally just fall down to
the floor you get me like I needed to
have 50k saved up so I can make the move
of getting my own crib getting a whip
whatever the case is right and then
obviously like kind of this is something
that like I've seen Steve do it I don't
know if you know who Steve would do it
is um I've heard it many on a lot of
other podcasts like once you do that big
step like it forces you to grind to get
more stuff yeah so it's almost like the
art of like giving to get back so like
if you spend money on whatever it is
like you're going to get the money back
times more absolutely so I feel like
that's kind of like when I did those
moves like more money started coming in
because then I started think in a
different way you like it put me in a
different position to think differently
yeah so and I and I give a lot of credit
to myself sister um I when I first
started my trading journey I was living
in an apartment um out there by my
college but I moved back to Detroit and
I'm living with my sister so I was able
to save my money and um be able to grow
my account without have to spend so much
you know what I'm saying so I gave a lot
of credit to my sister for letting me
just live with her nice for like a year
so that really that really helped me I'm
not going to lie like not having no
bills like that like that really help
that [__] does help bro yeah it do how
the bills now stacking up the Miami
bills are crazy if you want to live in
Miami you're going to pay a lot of money
I'm telling you right now you're going
to pay a lot bro like like just living
here alone is is crazy but then like you
got to live this certain standard it's
even crazier bro like this [__] just
starts adding up yeah Miami is like like
it's own thing so I mean so you said you
you learned from somebody you learn from
fibs on live shout out to fibs on Li um
then you kind of remix like your own
trading from it like you kind of like
now stick to just supply and demand like
Market structure yeah so I trade
supplying demand I trade liquidity grass
but mainly supplying demand really took
my trade to the next level like I just
can't lie like it's really just
supplying demand and then how many
trades do you take a day uh one or two
trades I trade Monday Tuesday Thursday
Friday don't trade on Wednesdays I get
that question all the time it's part of
my trading plan um really in my opinion
I feel like trading every single day
just don't work that's just my opinion
so I literally chose a day to take off
and it was Wednesday so that's really
what it was I get that question all the
time pretty interesting not going to lie
so how do you feel if like your trade
setup that you were doing on Wednesday
plays out like how do you feel I don't
feel like anything I see setups happen
on Wednesday but I mean I was the
trading plan that I used I was using it
for years so that's really has helped me
to grow my account not overtrade so I
just stick to my trading plan so even if
I see a setup on Wednesday I don't care
and a couple of my students would still
take the setup on Wednesday and they'll
win but I'm so disciplined with my
trading plan I'm not going to break it
that's fire yeah I mean it's kind of
like I have the same thing but just for
Sunday I don't take trades on Sundays
like the market open um my Approach is
very different to yours like I know
you're like on the lower time frames I'm
obviously like on the higher time frames
so like I kind of got to let for like
those weekly Wicks to like build out
you're probably catching those like
smaller moves which are a lot more
volatile like it get you one or two
trades a day it's pretty dope I've never
heard of anybody say no trades on a
Wednesday cuz like Wednesday is supposed
to like the best days are supposed to be
Tuesday Wednesday Thursday like the most
vol days cuz they like the middle of the
week what other like like like trading
rule do you have like that like that's
like different that's different is
unorthodox I mean I don't know Wednesday
is just not a good day um I avoid news I
don't like trading news um I only take
the setups that come during my session I
don't trade outside of my session so
it's only 8:00 a.m. to 11:00 a.m. that's
it New York that's it three hours out of
the day I'm after that I'm not trading
anymore so you're not and you're not
going to hold out of that session no I'm
not going to hold so if the trade
doesn't move within that session to your
take profit you're you're out of it yeah
I'm out of it I'm going for sure and
then like you won't have anything like
let's say you're up one to one put a
break even let it go or just you're
completely out yeah so like um if I'm
twin trading and it reach a one1 r I
will move my stop loss to break even and
leave it for a longer term Target
whether that's liquidity or more gaps to
field but um most of the time like if
I'm really like honestly I be having
stuff to do in the morning so like I
would just close my position at 101 mhm
and then I just have to handle my
business so like I don't leave Runners
all the time but yeah yeah that's pretty
dope that's kind of it's kind of like
the same thing we have a buddy of ours
his name is AB I don't know you know AB
he does kind of the same thing but in
London but he'll like literally let it
right out from London to New York
because the trade literally just catches
both sessions at once because after New
York it kind of dies down because market
closes and all that kind of stuff so
that's pretty interesting I mean outside
like of trading when you're not trading
like what do you do like there's a lot
of to do here in Miami when I'm not
balling you up like like what what are
you doing I mean I like playing
basketball I play a lot of
basketball play video games I beat by
the way in basketball he cannot play
basketball y' don't don't let him lie to
y'all okay so what do you do um I mean I
really just like the nature of Miami I
like being in the water like anything
involving water I have to be a part of
it like whether it's on boat jet skis
like or swimming or whatever like I need
to be buy some water so I really just
like any water activity that's what I'm
about to do so outside of so when you're
done from your set from 8 to 11: you're
not looking at the charts for the rest
of the day um I may like review the
setup that I just taken but other than
that like I'm just chilling or I'm
answering questions or or I'm just in
the chat just talking to um the Discord
or whatever I feel like a big issue like
even to like sometimes like it happens
to me and like a lot of new upcoming
Traders is like they think the more time
they spend on the charts the more
they're going to make because they're
like coming out from like a job like oh
like the more I hustle the more I make
it's like overtime you work overtime the
more money you make but that's kind of
not the case in trading you feel me like
it's almost like the less you're on the
charts the more you make and that's true
people ask me all the time do you mark
up your charts the night before do you
um do you have something set up before
you wake up in the morning trade and I
tell them no every single time like when
I when I when I take my setups it's just
a fresh new setup that's being created
that day I'm not marking up like
different time frames and waiting on it
to come I'm all already on the five
minutes so I don't really have to do
that I'm just taking the setups as they
come you know so I don't do a lot of
like I honestly I don't even back test
like that I'm G be honest like I really
don't do a lot of back testing no more I
used to do a lot of back testing but now
I'll do like 30 minutes and I'll be good
I mean because I feel like I feel like
when you back test you like yeah like
it's dope you get to see previous price
but you're not like looking at patterns
that you're going to see in the live
marketly you're when you're back testing
you're not taking into consideration the
time you're taking the trade you're not
taking into consideration the day cuz
you're not going to go down like it
tells you the time you're not going to
go on the calendar and match the
calendar with the day like I'm sure know
every Monday or Tuesday Market's going
to move a certain way and so then
Wednesday Thursday Friday you know what
I mean yeah the only way you're going to
learn that is with live markets like you
got to be up to date and like how the
market was moving 5 10 years ago it's
really not the same now bro it's not the
same anymore at all like when people do
like those you do live trading right so
when people have like courses from like
three four years ago I'm like that's
dope that's going to set you a dope
Foundation to know what trading is but
just know the markets aren't going to
move the same there's going to be a lot
bigger wicks a lot faster moves a lot
slower moves you need to be in front of
the market every single day in order for
you to be able to understand how the
market is moving today like it's not
going to be moving how it was moving 5
years ago and 5 years from now it's not
going to be moving the same kind of how
your strategy evolved from fibs to now
like supplying the man exactly like do
you have a lot of like I've seen your
TRS before they're very simple you have
a couple lines and that's it like you
don't throw much on it yeah I don't
really have a lot of indicators um I use
moving averages but at the end of the
day like Market structure and
candlesticks is just priority number one
one um like yeah so so it's just like
the moving like an added Confluence like
yeah it's just like I I use like the
honey on top like the cherry on top yeah
moving averages they just like just an
additional help just to see if I'm going
right with the trend but the trend can
always change and moving averages
they're going to be that's the last
thing that's going to move when it when
the trend is changing so I don't really
rely on indicators too much like that's
you're you you're too late in the move
so I'm good and then when it when it
comes to like trading like before like
what would you say was like your biggest
issues that you were like having like
before completely like something that
you're like damn like I keep doing the
same exact thing like let me stop it um
trying to get my money back after losing
like for real like every time when I was
losing um it just really discouraged me
CU I felt like I'm getting further away
from my goal like I'm I'm not reaching
where I want to be at so it's like damn
let me try to get this money back
because I'm not progressing day by day
because when you're like grinding trying
to get out of your
job when you get a setback it's like
it's you feel bad it's like damn like
I'm not am I even capable of getting to
the next level so like me over trading
like I always wanted to just like make
my money back and that was hurting my
trading career so once I got really
discipline like it was really a deal
breaker as far as my success so and then
when you do discipline like what do you
do like you write things down you have
like a checklist like like how do you
keep yourself accountable for that
because I was telling Josh I was like
look bro when you work a job right for
example he works electricity you do the
electricity there's the inspector above
you then there's supervisor and then the
boss like all of these guys are
filtering out your work to them to make
sure everything was right so then the
super uh your boss make sure that your
work was good the supervisor makes sure
that the boss's job was good and it's
like a chain when it comes to trading
like you're that person for every single
one you're the one looking at your
trading plan you're the one looking at
your risk management looking at your
entries like looking at all these
different things and you're the one
holding yourself accountable yeah cuz if
you're not going to do it there's no
booss going to come like yo if you don't
do it right again like we're going to
fire you like right that's what happens
in a regular job so what do you do like
how do you hold yourself accountable in
trading um well at the beginning of my
journey I had a whiteboard right by my
computer I literally had it right there
and I used to write down my rules my
risk management the pars I'm going into
trade like my whole trading plan was on
the Whiteboard so even and the crazy
part about it even though I had my
whiteboard right there I still didn't
follow my rules it took me to bump my
head a few times to really lock in on my
trading plan so but that's really all I
did was just have a white board right
there by my my laptop when I was trading
to hold myself accountable I mean I have
the same thing just like a like sticky
notes I have like sticky notes like all
over like the computer yeah but like cuz
like I like there still be days where
like I break my trading rules today cuz
like kind of when you're like when you
have like more room for buffer that
you've made some nice profits like
sometimes those lower risk trades like
they give you a higher risk reward and
sometimes it's worth the risk like you
know you never know like um but whenever
I break one of my rules like I have um I
have this rule so like I love sweets bro
I love sweets a lot like if I don't like
if I don't eat a sweet after a meal like
I I will feel bad like I literally won't
feel like like I'll literally have like
a stomach ache like I need to eat even
it's like of a small piece of chocolate
this big so if that day if I broke my
rule can't have that chocolate oh wow
let me tell you I want that chocolate
bad bro like I want that little piece of
chocolate bad but every single time I go
take a trade and I'm like damn this is
not against I mean this is not going
with my rules is this worth not eating
that chocolate later so I'm holding
myself accountable knowing that damn
there is going to be a precaution if I
don't do what I'm supposed to so there's
times where I've literally caught myself
and I'm like you know what I want that
chocolate later and I avoid myself from
having a loss but then there's times
where like I could have done it and I
would have made money but it's just like
what's right or wrong you I mean so
that's kind of like something that helps
me keep myself accountable that's dope
yeah it's like it's like a little like
like psychology tip it's like trust me I
want that chocolate bad bro yeah I feel
that I feel you bro I mean what are like
some things that you know cuz like
trading is cool but like I feel like
there's so much more to like a Trader
than trading absolutely you mean like
charts are gangster you know but like
I'm also human you know like I I do a
lot of other stuff other than trading
like too like you know me because of
trading but there's a whole other side
of me so like what's that other side of
you I mean it just depends on what
people want to no I'm I'm a private
person like I'm very lowkey I don't like
sharing too much um I didn't even share
like apartment tour like when I moved
into my new apartment I didn't even
share that cuz I'm just very private but
I mean I'm just like you like I'm just
like a regular person like having fun
like socializing like you know just
being a regular human being I'm 25 like
I'm just young I just want to have fun
but I'm very private like I don't like
sharing too much like I really don't and
then like what would you say is like
your plan like let's say the next like
do you have a plan like let's say next
six months two year because bro I'm
telling you coming to Miami is huge like
what you just did bro it's big you're
going to be around people that are going
to take you to the next level like what
what would be like what is your road map
like what do you see for yourself like
you see trading forever CU I'm I'm going
be straight up bro I'm I'm probably not
like this whole social media thing this
whole like YouTube thing like this is
cool like enjoy while you have it cuz
I'm not about to be here in the next
year like I want to live my own life you
I mean like I'm putting all this work
doing all this content take advantage
cuz it's going to get to the time where
I want to do me exactly just do whatever
I want to doly and just not talk about
it just live my life you get absolutely
so like I kind of have a road map set up
for me in the next 6 to 12 months like
what like what do you have kind of set
up um I feel like I'm going to be like
honestly I feel like I'm going to be
trading and still posting content for
probably like two three more years and
I'm going to slow down like on per I'm
going to slow down on purpose um I think
I'm not even going to be in Miami in the
next few years to be honest I'm just
here for like a just like I said it's a
n work but um I'm definitely probably
going to try to get into more passive
income type of um like an industry
that's just passive cuz again like we
still have to wake up and trade like
we're not this is we're making money
like in a in a high speed but at the
same time we still have to show up so I
definitely want to get into something
that's more passive where I don't have
to do too much even though we not really
doing much but just we're just trading
you know but yeah I definitely want to
get into something that's more passive
like real estate or something like that
I mean bro like when people like say
like bro like trading is as passive as
get it's like like I don't think you
understand like it's not it's not
passive like I got to wake up every cuz
I wake up just like you I wake up at
6:00 every day like bro like I got to
wake up and I got to like think hard
like what I'm about to do like I got to
like it's like torture on like it really
is torture like like it really is if you
think about it like we're here like
about to click a button it either goes
good or goes bad we have to just like
take this whole tedious like like
rundown of like what are we're about to
do and if we do it good like there's so
much to it that it's not b like it's
it's not passive at all it takes more of
a toe on you than an actual job cuz in a
job you just you're set to do certain
things and then you go home you go home
you're done like bro if you break like
let's say that right now you enter
losing stream like that like that [__]
will affect everything bro you know I've
been on a losing streak before it
affected me I felt like I wasn't good I
felt what was your biggest losing streak
um I W I think I lost five trades in a
row okay that's chilling that's really
not that bad I mean but it depend on how
much your lots are so I yeah I lost a
lot lot of money and it it really it
made me feel like I wasn't capable of
trading even though I had profitability
for months and months and months it just
that losing streak really discouraged me
but it's like an uncertain outcome bro
like you don't know when you're going to
get out of it you got mean so it's kind
of scary like you don't cuz like like
we're like we know how to trade but we
don't know when the plus is coming we
don't know when the negative is coming
so like that un uncertainty it creates
like this tension bro even to me to like
to to this day man like like like for
example I had my biggest winning streak
14 weeks I just had a losing streak for
two weeks bro I'm two weeks I'm not
talking about five trades I'm talking
about like 10 trades that I lost back to
back like you know what it is I'm
getting up every single day doing
everything I'm supposed to following
your rules bro just doing everything
else I click the button and just boom
stop loss boom stop loss and I'm just
like bro what am I doing wrong then last
when you start entering doubt you start
entering I say you know what we'll come
back tomorrow and do the same thing and
tomorrow will be a better day keep you
come tomorrow and boom again lose again
for two whole weeks man like that [__]
takes a toll on you that nobody will
ever go through in a job cuz in a job
like let's say you're doing your job and
something goes wrong the boss and the
owner take it like you know you just go
do something else so like trading it is
not passive income it's not ever get get
out your head it's not ever it's not do
you believe in Bots like trading Bots um
Bots yeah a little bit little bit I have
faith in them bro you you have faith in
Bots I have a bot you have a bot yeah
it's swing trading bot um it's got like
like a mix of like a little bit of
everything but like like it's not like a
full automatic bot like it's just like I
actually have to manually it like I have
to go in every single day turn it on
turn it off you I mean like so it's not
fully passive but to a certain extent
you're trying to get it passive yeah I I
I hope in the next like five years some
somebody some very smart you know Mark
Zuckerberg or Bill Gates whatever yeah
build some [__] and I just throw my
money and you do your thing man I'll
give you a profit split a lot of people
don't approve um Bots what you what you
think what you think about the I mean I
think I think it will go down but like
it'll never be like for us like as
investors it will be fully passive but
there's somebody behind that screen
clicking some buttons every day without
a doubt so that so you think it is
somebody that's behind the scen yeah
there has to be somebody monitoring I
don't ever think like bro like the
market for example let's say right now
um Biden Biden falls down the stairs or
does some [__] like the Market's going
crazy right because it just it is what
it is yeah but then like a bot will
never know how to read that cuz they
don't know who Biden is they don't know
he just felt they don't know none of
that stuff there's no way it could or at
least to my knowledge there's no way it
could read fundamentals that way or like
an event happening that fast I feel
that's why a lot of bots like mess up
cuz they get caught in those moves but I
think if there is a team or somebody
behind that bot making sure it doesn't
mess up and turning it off in those
moments I think it could be successful I
really do I really do think that's just
my opinion but it would it would never
be fully automatic there has to be a
team behind it monitoring at all times
if not it wouldn't not work out yeah I
don't believe in that fully automa I
feel so other than real estate like what
else are you looking to kind of like
invest into um some Amazon stores I have
two stores bro yeah I definitely want to
get into some Amazon stuff um you should
bro I have two stores build your credit
um passive income like I don't like I
literally do nothing the guy that I have
he just bro amazing guy I can set you up
with him if you want sure he probably
I'll get him to not charge you that much
bro cuz like the way the way I see it
like I want to have other sources of
income outside of trading for sure I
don't want to just depend on trading I
want to like go on a month do my own
thing and still make money you know i'ms
are working I'm probably making like
prob like four 5K each store month
that's dope chill but there like a
Snowball Effect you got to wait for the
store to like build up which is kind of
annoying it's like it's like you're
trading account like you start off small
and you build it up and we're in the
fourth quarter so this is probably some
good time to have an Amazon store cuz
like the Christmas I mean bro my guy
sells like this this how you know there
like a bunch of different Industries
like you can literally sell anything
like this guy's selling like it's like
you know like those air purifiers this
guy's making bank off and things cuz
like he'll make them in China and then
like ship them over here he does FBA or
FBI or whatever FBA yeah not FBI not not
those guys
FBA yeah so he does FBA he'll like make
the product bring it down and then he
like remixes it put a label and ships it
out that's good okay yeah so I mean we
talked a little bit about trading talked
about your journey
uh I mean like what would be like one of
your biggest tips that you could tell to
Doyle back in Detroit that like that was
just like just not having it man like
like like going through the struggles
like what would you tell to doy back
then I would tell him to be patient um
focus on yourself it's it's hard when
you're on your journey and you seeing so
many Traders be successful and you're
not successful focus on yourself use it
as inspiration and motivation but still
focus on your journey um um and just
stay consistent man cuz it was sometimes
I'm like man I might have to just stop
like I it's not working so but something
back of my head was like just keep going
so I would tell my younger self a couple
years ago just stay consistent man focus
on yourself don't get discouraged man
it's going to happen sure and then what
would you say would be your top three
biggest mistakes that got to where you
are and then your top three biggest
accomplishments that got you to where
you are okay top three biggest mistakes
was jumping into a live account too soon
um I felt like I was ready
to make some real money cuz I was on
demo but U once I went to a live account
it was just completely different so I
advise Traders if you're new take your
time when you're trading on demo to
transition to a live account take your
time um another mistake I would probably
say it's just not following my trading
plan like the trading plan is literally
the foundation of my trading career I
need the trading plan to be on point so
um just me just breaking my trading plan
with was really hurting me like I just
kept breaking my rules I have my rules
right in front of me and I just keep
breaking it don't know why but like I
said like you're going to have to bump
your head before you can start taking it
to the next level and uh the last
mistake um over consuming too much
knowledge that really was like it's so
much information out there that it can
it can really get overwhelming so like
slow down like focus on one like one
aspect of Forex and then transition to
the next don't consume too much because
it's gonna overwhelm you so I that's
definitely a mistake that I did yeah I
definitely agree like if you just want
to do support and resistance just do
supporting resistance don't add
supporting resistance then add fibs and
then add EMAs and add and just add all
this [__] you can't even see the charts
bro man so then what would be the top
three biggest things you like that
you've accomplished that got you to
where you are today the top three um
I'll probably say like the longest
winning streak I went on I think I went
on like seven winning streak I had like
11k week that's was like one of my like
biggest weeks that was like a huge
accomplishment
um another accomplishment I mean moving
out here is a big accomplishment not
going lie I'm from a I'm not from a
small town but like if you've been from
Detroit you understand I'm from the East
side of Detroit it's very tough over
there so me moving out here from Forex
was like a big deal I'm like wow I'm
really doing it big like it really it I
was proud and uh the last accomplishment
I would probably say um
me just touching people like across the
world like far as my psychology videos
cuz people love my psychology videos I
don't know why but people really connect
with me like I get DMS all the time like
man I really appreciate you for making
these videos like so I probably say my
psychology videos moving out here and um
having that 11k week that was like a big
deal for me fire yeah we got to make
sure you turn those into 11k days bro
trust me when you start compounding that
[__] goes crazy yeah man I'm going to
get there man I'm going to get there
fire yo appreciate you bro getting on
the podcast um we got some big things if
you guys haven't seen the video with
Josh he's at the end of the video with
Josh he gives Jos some tips Josh the guy
from McDonald's so um appreciate you bro
see you guys in the next episode take
easy guys peace